Hello Hello, I'm from the city of
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте я из города
Khmelnitsky Where am I from, from the Una region of
Хмельницкий Вы откуда я с унской области
Russia And what city is there? I only
России А город какой там я только
know Ulyanovsk in this area, I
Ульяновск знаю в этой области я с
understood from the village and the World Cup you communicate there Yes, this is the
деревни понял а ЧМ общаетесь там Да я
first time I've come in. Actually, this is the first
вообще первый раз зашёл Вообще первый
time I'm your first person in chatroulette.
раз я у вас первый человек в чатрулетке
Yes, well  not the first one here, now the tenth scale
Да ну не первый тут десятый сейчас шкал
is here, why did you go to Ukraine, they
тут а зачем вы зашли в Украину
just chose so that Russia would not be
выбрали просто чтобы не Россия была
put in Ukraine And why are you embarrassed
поставил Украину А что вам стрёмно с
to communicate with the Russians, no, you just wanted to
россиянами общаться нет просто хотелось
see to know your
увидеть узнать
neighbors And why didn’t the Chinese take
соседей А китайцы в че не взяли
you into Chinese, you don’t know how to speak Chinese yet Well, maybe there
вы по-китайски ещё не умею Ну может там
in English Talk to the
по-английски Поговорите с
Chinese Pony
китайцем Поня
and yes yes yes
и да да
and what interests you what do you want Yes
да и что вас интересует что вы хотите Да
I’m a blogger blogger here
я блогер блогер тут
people catch Russians from Russia how I catch them
людей ловите русских с россие как ловлю
so I drive away On what topics do you catch And on the
так прогоняю На какие темы ловите А на
topic of
тему
war why did Russia attack yes no here
войны за что напала Россия да нет вот
first
сначала
first first  I’m asking you, for example,
сча сначала спрашиваю вот Вас например
how do you feel about the war against Ukraine
как вы относитесь к войне против Украины
? Well, how did I have to
Ну как пришлось так
say that
сказать
? Oh, damn, there’s such nonsense sitting in the [ __ ] village of the
Ой блин сидит кая чепуха в деревне [__]
Ulyanovsk region, this is tough, where there’s
Ульяновской области это жесть где
some kind of ass of the world, and I’m telling you that I
какая-то [__] мира да и рассказываю что
had to attack Ukraine. Why did you
пришлось напасть на Украину А почему вы
decide that the ass of the world is the question  Yes, it’s a good
решили что [__] мира вопрос Да хороший
question, everything is well-reasoned, they immediately ask
вопрос все аргументировано сразу просят
for an argument. Why is it an ass? Yes, from your
аргументировать Почему [__] Да из вашей
village, so let’s start. So,
деревни так вот Давайте начнём Так вы В
what countries have you been to? And what difference does it make where I’ve
каких странах были А какая разница где я
been? What does it mean? Well, let’s do it
был Что это означает Вот вот вот давайте
like this in Russia. You were from your village,
так в России г Вы были из своей деревни
where did you go? I  and in the Krasnoyarsk Territory
куда вы выезжали Я и в Красноярском крае
in Penza in Samara there
в Пензе в Самаре
was what were you doing there that somewhere tourism
был что вы там делали что где-то туризм
somewhere somewhere work was driving around I
где-то где-то работа по работе гоняла
understood yes 50 to 5050 Yes uh look in
понял да 50 на 5050 Да ээ смотрите в
your your village Yes there is gas there is yes
вашей вашей деревне Да есть газ есть
How many inhabitants do you have  there 1500
есть да Сколько жителей у вас там 1500
15500 And what kind of village is this at
15500 А что это такое за деревня на
15500 Well, tell me, I’ll look on the map now, I’m
15500 Ну скажите я сейчас на карте
interested Ulyanovsk
посмотрю мне интересно Ульяновская
region Nikolaev district Well, then there’s
область Николаевский район Ну а дальше
no need
ни к
[music]
[музыка]
Now I’m just looking at your interior and
Сейчас я просто смотрю на интерьер ваш и
I understand that in the village there’s sadness in
я понимаю что в селе печалька в деревне
this village  so Nikolaevsky
этой так Николаевский
district Yes, the [ __ ] of the world
район Да срака мира
In short, not the only thing that exists, but that the
Короче не единственное что есть да что
route is shorter Moscow Talya
трасса короче Москва талья
is nearby Well, the only thing is that you
рядом Ну вот Единственное что вас вы по
determine the state of all of Russia on the map, yes,
карте определяете состояние всей России
let's now look at the news like this Yes, in short, well, the
да давайте сейчас смотрим так новости
news is that a drunk burned out, that's
короче ну новость это пьяный сгорел это
all you have there  they're drinking Yes, but how
такое у вас там все бухают Да а как вы
did you determine that everyone is drinking? You're not drinking,
определили что все бухают у вас не буха
but maybe some interesting news
а можете что какие-то интересные новости
about your Nikolaev district of the Ulyanovsk
про вашу Николаевский район Ульяновской
region. I'm wondering what's
области Вот мне интересно что там
going on there, social life,
происходит социальная жизнь как-то там
cultural life, what kind of
культурная жизнь какая ремонт
road repairs, social cultural life,
дорог социа культурная жизнь
who's  you're celebrating the district's birthday
Кто у вас День рождения района
Wait Stop stop stop I
проводят Подожди Стоп стоп стоп я
found the photos Damn I'm specifically
фотографии нашёл Блин мне вот конкретно
yours Where are you Going to the
ваши ваши А вы куда Заходите в
forbidden network VKontakte Nope I'm going
запрещённую сеть ВКонтакте нене захожу
to Google I'm typing Ulyanovsk region
вот в Гугле набираю Ульяновская область
Nikolaev district and there's just crap here
Николаевский район и там просто срань
Teplovka Teplovka - this is in your
вот Тепловка Тепловка - это в вашем
area
районе есть
Holy [ __ ]
[__]
there's some kind of former palace there I even see
там какой-то бывший дворец Даже вижу
an estate Yes, the estate is an estate Well, it
усадьба Да усадьба есть усадьба Да ну
was more accurate to say correctly the estate
была точнее сказать правильно усадьба
was all that was left of it was
была от неё осталась только срака
just [ __ ] ass And you What are you proud of
просто [__] А у вас Чем гордитесь
now now no you don't get off now
сейчас сейчас нене вы не слезайте сейчас
I'm completely Well you crap on me so to
я полностью Ну вы обосрали меня так
speak Not yet  they didn’t [ __ ] I’m just me just
сказать Не ещё не обосрали Я только я
searl a little bit
только серл немножко
on the floor So let’s at
на пол шишки Так давайте хоть вы
least say something of
что-нибудь восх
your own at us you’re
своё на нас вы говном кидаете вентилятор
throwing [ __ ] at the fan now it’s not us now there’s a whole
накидывается сечас не мы сечас целый
dump truck what are you proud of
самосвали чем вы гордитесь
and you By the way, your nationality is Chuvash
а вы Кстати по национальности вы чуваш
no And
нет А
who is the best person to support the war  that
кто классно рз поддерживает войну то
is, you were occupied by the
есть вас оккупировали
Muscovites, you can’t support the war, I
московиты войну поддерживать нельзя я с
talked to a normal person Yes, he understands
нормальным общался Да он понимает да что
that Moscow is
типа Москва
its own for me, it’s interesting, that is, you said
сво по мне интересно то есть ты сказали
I support in Erzya, you really Erzya
Я поддерживаю во эрз ты реально эрзя
support these
поддерживаешь вот этих оккупантов
Russian occupiers who are pumping out
российских которые выкачивают
yours, you don’t have anything at all, you have  in
твои не нет у вас вообще ничего у вас в
this
этой
crap in your Nikolaev region, in general, there’s no
хре в твоей Николаевской области вообще
[ __ ] way, you don’t have a
ой районе Вообще нихера нет у вас не
war, you have civilizations No, I’m looking at
войны у вас цивилизации Нет я смотрю по
the photographs You tell me specifically the
фотографи Ты скажи конкретно населённые
settlements so that I can press you in general You’re
пункт чтобы я вообще поджал ты
embarrassed, so I can name the city of Khmelnitsky
стесняешься вот я город Хмельницкий могу
You can come and see And
назвать Ты можешь зайти посмотреть А
this is a baevka baevka  I had a grandfather a couple of days ago,
баевка баевка это у меня пару дней назад
he spoke to him, his father was from
был дед он говорил с у него отец был из
the battlefield, too, Ulyanovsky, it’s just a
баевке тоже Ульяновский это просто
joke, he was in the war, I was his No, you
прикол он в войну был я егос Да нет вы
tell me when you declare war, then
скажите когда объявите войну то сами
why the hell should you declare war, well, you’ve been
Нахрена вам Объявлять войну ну вы же с
fighting the region with us since 1914
нами с четырнадцатого года воюете
Now I’ll see what you’ve
область Сейчас я баевка посмотрю что
been doing since
делаете с четырнадцатого
1914. Spring walk in the village of
года Родник гуляй село
baevka,
баевка
so I’m
так всё улы
smiling now, look here, these are
баю сейчас смотри тут такие
cool things you recently got gas in. Yes,
классные вам недавно газ провели Да
why recently is it like how recently did we
почему недавно это как насколько недавно
just get gas in 1414? Well,
че четырнадцатом году только провели газ
I realized this recently, this is recently, Yes,
Ну я понял это недавно это недавно Да
almost 10  Ukraine hasn’t started bombing the bamboo for years yet.
почти 10 лет ещё Украина бамбас не
Yes, and that
начала бомбить Да и что
you were still without gas, I understood that is,
Вы ещё без газа сидели я понял то есть
when Russia
когда Россия
invades again, I say that you still
вторгается ещё раз говорю то у вас ещё
didn’t have gas there, I understood, yes, that
не было газа до сих пор там понял да то
is, not the entire region is now
есть у вас не весь район сейчас
gasified one way or another  Well,
газифицирован так или ве А ну процентов
85 percent, yes, that is, look at your E I won’t
85 да то есть смотри ваш Э не буду
say the ass of the world is yours God-forgotten
говорить [__] мира ваш Богом Забытый
region has not yet been gasified,
район ещё до сих пор не газифицирован
now we will see how
сейчас мы посмотрим насколько он
gasified it is, you say
газифицирован вы говорите
yes Well, approximately the region
да Ну примерно район
Yes, our ass of the world is no different from your
Да наша [__] мира не отличается от вашей
ass of the
жопы
world gasification of Ukraine how much  Wait
мира газификация Украины сколько Подожди
wait sis Well, you are attacking the
подожди сес Ну вы накидывается на
fan and you are them. Look, 78% of
вентилятор а сами них Вот смотри 78% у
you have gasification now, that is, you have everything in the
вас газификация сейчас то есть у вас все
entire Una region, you are now
всей унской области вы сейчас
Nikolaevsky district Nikolaevsky district I
Николаевский район Николаевский район я
took the news
взял вот новость
Well, it turns out that the Great Gas
Ну получается что Великая газовая
Power can drive
держава может загнать в Европу
a gas pipeline to Europe but not  maybe all the
газопровод но не может все населённые
settlements of the Nikolaev region Why so and
пункты Николаевской области Почему так а
how
как происходит
gasification is happening I don’t know I know that the
газификация Я не знаю Я знаю что
main gas pipeline is being laid, a
прокладывается основной газопровод
large pipe which in this case
большая труба которая в данном случае
went to Europe in this case through
шла в Европу в данном случае через
Ukraine Yes from which there were branches to the
Украину Да от которой шли ответвления в
side already additionally inside
сторону уже дополнительно внутри
Russia So why gasify everything
России Так почему всего газифицировать
those sections that are near a large pipe
те участки которые возле большой трубы
Yes, already small sections, other sections are already
Да уже мелкие участки другие участки уже
heavier, the first 70 are always easy gas and the
тяжелее первые 70 всегда легко гази а
remaining 30 are always heavier, slower,
остальные 30 всегда тяжелее медленнее
and that yes, and the question is again Why is
идут и что да и вопрос ещё раз Почему
Russia a great power that has
Россия великая держава у которой есть
gas, oil, diamonds, it sells to the whole world
газ нефть алмазы она продаёт всему миру
Yeah, this world  maybe you are
Угу этот мир может утебя в Германии
gasified in Germany? Yes, it comes all the way from Russia,
газифицирован Да приходит аж из России
but you still can’t cover the
герни ва а у вас не могут покрыть
Ulyanovsk region with gas.
ульяновскую область до сих пор газом
Why
Почему
is 78% by settlement or by
А 78% это по населённым пунктам или по
population, you
населению вы
look now writes 78 about now I’ll
смотрите сейчас пишет 78 про сейчас
clarify By what
уточню По какому
parameter
параметру так
is it always harder?  spend where
ведь всегда тяжелее провести где
10 the overall level of gasification in the Ulyanovsk
10 общий уровень газификации Ульяновской
region is now 78% I don’t know
области сейчас составляет 78% Я не знаю
the share of gasified housing in And look Dude,
доля газифицирован во А смотри Чувак в
currently in Niko this is the end of the
настоящее время в Нико это конец д
second year at the present time in the
второго года в настоящем время в
Nikolaev region 21
Николаевском районе газифицирован 21
settlements are gasified, the share of
населённый пункт доля
gasified housing has gas, that is,
газифицированном жилья имеет газ то есть
more than
больше
half  life in my village
половины житло в моём селе газ
there is gas even about
есть даже про
7 that is, yes in your village not everyone has
7 то есть да в твоём селе не все имеют
gas Not everyone Not everyone yes Many even
газ Не все Не все да Многие даже сами
refuse gas themselves and look And
отказываются от газа да и смотри И по
look in the Nikolaev district in
смотри по по николаевскому району по
your district of the Ulyanovsk region more than
твоему району Ульяновской области больше
half of the people are sitting without
половины людей сидит без
gas because What they write is that the share of
газа потому Что пишут что доля
housing is gasified Almost half Yes, I don’t
газифицирован жилья Почти половина Да не
know what the overall level of
знаю что означает общий уровень
gasification in the Ulyanovsk region 78% means, what is
газификации Ульяновской области 78% что
this then not for populated areas or
это тогда не по населённым пунктам или
for what? Yes, but for houses if for residential ones Yes, it
по чем Да но по домам если по жилым Да
turns out that half of the people are sitting without
выходит что половина людей сидит без
gas for 23 years  half of the people you yourself
газа 23 год не половина людей вы сами
said it doesn’t say how much is
сказали там не написано сколько по
written Look, that’s not how it says 78, this is the
написано Смотри не вот как пишет 78 это
general level of gasification I don’t know what
общий уровень газификации Я не знаю что
it is, but they write the share is gasified, that
это да а пишут доля газифицирован ль то
is, housing, yes Almost half, that is,
есть жилья да Почти половина то есть
housing, one person lives or what’s the
жилье один человек живёт или во какая
difference Well, housing  here are the houses If we
разница Ну жилья вот дома Если мы
look at the apartments This is the same as what yours are
смотрим кварти Это то же самое что ваши
saying
говорят
now that in Russia half of the
сейчас что в России нету у половины
country doesn’t have half of the houses don’t have gas in
страны половина домов не имеет газ вот
your words here your sources
вашими словами вот ваши ваши источники
also write that half of Russia does not have
ещё пишут что половина России не имеет
access to sewerage This is not me saying
доступа к канализации Это не я говорю
sri These are yours  look, I'm in the Google room,
сри Это ваши вот смотри я зал Google
now I'm helping
сечас мне помога
me and I'm saying that in my village where there is
я и говорю что в моём же селе где есть
gas, gas has been installed on every street,
газ проведён по каждой улице газ
everyone who wants can
проведён каждый желающий Кто хочет может
get it, but not everyone gets it installed. Why don't they
провести Но не все проводят А почему не
suddenly get gas installed? Well, I have no idea. Well, that's
проводят вдруг газ Ну я без понятия Ну
why  70% of you wanted gas and
вот почему вот у вас 70% пожелала газ а
30% weren’t for it Yes, there it is, there it is Well, I
30% не за Да вон где он там он Ну вот
see yes There’s that meter Yes, what
вижу да Вон этот счётчик Да что
happened so that
случилось так что
30% of them there want your fellow villagers didn’t
30% они там хотят ваших односельчан не
want gas But I don’t give a damn Well, that’s
захотели газ Та мне насрать Ну вот а
why I have no idea about them  I don’t ask
почему так без понятия я их не спрашиваю
Well, what do you
Ну как
think? No idea Well, what happened that
думаете Без понятия Ну что случилось что
people didn’t want to supply gas? Well,
люди не захотели газ провести Ну да
why do people in the village refuse
из-за чего люди в селе отказываются
to supply gas? It’s their business, well, interesting.
проводить газ это их дело ну интересно
Well, well, you have some guesses.
Ну как Ну у вас есть какие-то догадки Ну
Well, tomorrow I’ll ask you, I’ll tell you tomorrow  no Well,
вот завтра спрошу вам скажу завтра не Ну
what do you think, they don’t have money, maybe
вот а как думаете у них денег нет может
yes Or they don’t know what, why don’t we have a
да Или они не знаю что почему нет у нас
free supply to the house yes a free supply to the house
до дома подвод бесплатный да до дома
Yes, but for some reason they don’t
подвод бесплатный Да но что-то они не
deliver in the World Cup Why didn’t they bring you
подводят в ЧМ Почему не подвели
for free once say
бесплатно е раз
what do you think if  in your village they will
гово как думаете если у вас в селе будут
give out for free, for example,
бесплатно раздавать например
1000 rubles, they will come to take everything.
1000 рублей придут все
No idea, most of them
взять Без понятия большинство прит в
may
Может
have gas, why 30% of people
у проводит газ почему 30% людей не прове
didn’t install gas. No idea, I again. No
не провели газ Без понятия я ещё раз Без
idea, yes, that is, look, we,
понятия понял да то есть смотри мы
uh, looked Who are you from?  -the [ __ ] of
ээ посмотрели Кто ты из какой-то жопы
the world Yes, really the same ass as yours
мира Да реально такая же [__] как и ваша
No no not ours Look and it turns out you
Нет нет не наша Смотри и получается ты
look you are sitting in a state
смотри ты сидишь в государстве
gas station you have a huge Wait
бензоколонки у тебя огромнейший Подожди
I’ll tell you now Look you are sitting
я тебе сейчас расскажу Смотри ты сидишь
in a state gas station yes who do you
в государственной бензоколонке да ко вы
want
хотеть
Yes I impose with I  I really want to impose
Да я навязать с Я же так хочу навязать
my opinion on you. Why am I still talking to you?
своё мнение вам А зачем я с вами ещё
Yes, and you, instead of
буду говорить Да и вы вместо того чтобы
asking your state, why the hell
спросить своё государство А какого хрена
can’t even
у нас до сих пор не могут
more than half of our
газифицировать больше половины даже
households be gasified, and why are some more than
домохозяйств да почему ках каких больше
half of yours, or perhaps
половины ваших то во скаже
less?  Nikolaevsky e times for special
меньше в Николаевском е раз для особо
areas I read on the website on
оных области Читаю на сайте на в
basically yes, the second end of the twenty-
основном да д второй конец двадцать
second year, the share of housing is gasified.
второго года доля газифицирован жилья
Almost half That is, not even half of you
Почти половина То есть даже не половина
understand, you’re
понимаешь
sitting, starting Yes, they did the right thing, they
вы сидите начинаете Да правильно сделали
attacked the [ __ ] How much of your money was
напали бляблябля Сколько денег ваших
thrown into this war you are sitting, how much is being
вкид в эту войну ты сидишь сколько
thrown off  you're sitting in
скидывают ты сидишь на
front of the [ __ ]
фоне уёбищный
curtains of these trellises, what the hell is this in Russian,
штор этих шпалер как это бля по-русски
wallpaper and curtains, and you think how
обое обоев и занавесок Да и думаешь Как
good it is that they're there somewhere, you've
хорошо что они там короче где-то ты
never been abroad in your life, it's
никогда в жизни не был за границей
true, that rag behind you isn't [ __ ] disgusting. Oppa,
правда ва тряпка позади не уёбищная Опа
you were once  abroad Tell me
ты когда-то был заграницей Вот скажи
honestly, why do I need to go abroad, everyone
честно а зачем мне Заграница вот все у
who doesn’t have money to go abroad says
кого нет денег на заграницу говорят
why should I go abroad, all of yours also
зачем мне Заграница все ваши также
say who were Maximum in the KMU or
говорят которые были Максимум в КМУ или
on the Sea of ​​Azov, everyone who has Look
на Азовском море все кто у кого Смотри
Everyone who has had
Все у кого
their feet washed in this way in the Sea of ​​Azov every time That
Так ноги мыли в Азовском море е раз То
yes, you have confirmed that you really
есть вы подтвердили что вы реально
live there, you are a beggar abroad, you are
живёте там нищеброд на заграницу вашу вы
a beggar there, you admit to yourself, you
нищеброд там вы признаете себе у вас
don’t have it, you don’t give a damn, you simply don’t have the
нету вам не насрать у вас просто нет
opportunity. If you had it,
возможности Если бы у вас было возможно
where do you know?
откуда вы знаете Мой доход я ещ
also waste from the wallpaper and from
вас не из одной ещ изр от обоев и от
your boring bread, look, if you
вашего скучного хлеба смотри если у вас
had the opportunity right now to take your own
была возможность вот сейчас взять себе
private plane and fly to Australia, you
личный самолёт и слетать в Австралию вы
would fly no, fly, no fly,
бы слетали нет слетали нет слетали
for example, if the world is an ass, if I
например если [__] мира вот если у меня
had the opportunity, yes, for example, take a
была возможность Да например взять на
weekend flight, for example  Buenos Aires
выходные слетать например в Буэнос Айрес
Yes, I would fly, but I don’t want to. But I
Да я бы слетал а я вот не хочу А я вот
want to go to Baikal, you want it. And when
на Байкал хочу вот хотите И когда вы
were you on Baikal? I can at any time, but
были на Байкале Я в любой момент могу а
when you were you couldn’t Yes And when you were, I
когда были не можете Да А когда были я
didn’t say that I was or that I’m asking.
не говорил что я был или что я спрашиваю
you want we have a reserve of money I
Вот вы хотите наме есть запас денег я
can be yes You want to go to Baikal
могу быть да Вот Вы хотите на Байкал
When you were on Baikal And I’m not saying
Когда вы были на Байкале А я не говорю
that I was I’m asking you were once
что я был Я спрашиваю вы были когда-то
on Baikal you weren’t just you want to go to
на Байкале не был просто хотите на
Baikal What’s stopping you from taking and going
Байкал А что вам мешает взять и поехать
to  Baikal just right now I don’t want to, so
на Байкал просто пока сейчас не хочу так
you’ll make apartments and go. That’s what you want. And
вы квартиры сделаю и поеду Так вы же
now you don’t want to, but a dream
хотите А теперь не хотите а мечта всегда
should always be a dream, that is, for you
должна быть мечтой то есть для вас
to go to the Dream buy in Bono Saros or
поехать на бай Мечта в Боно сарос или
wait, I understand correctly that for you
подожди я правильно понимаю что для вас
to travel around Russia is  dream
поехать по России - это мечта
No, not everywhere Once again from the Ulyanovsk
Нет не везде Ещё раз с Ульяновской
region to Baikal - it’s a dream you said
области на Байкал - это мечта вы сказали
it’s a
это
dream you called it a dream there are
мечта вы назвали это
some details there is a dream
мечтой есть некоторые детали есть мечта
yes that is, I dream
да то есть
of Baikal I’m right Yes I
на Байкал я мечтаю я правильно Да
understand that you have a dream from one region of
понимаю что у вас мечта из одной области
Russia to visit another region  In Russia,
России побывать в другой области России
I said at the beginning that I was in the
я я ещё в начале сказал что был и в
Krasnoyarsk Territory, it’s 5000 or
Красноярском крае это 5000 или
whatever it is, but you’re dreaming. And
сколько-то там но мечтаете нака А
how many years have you dreamed of
сколько лет вот как давно вы мечтали на
going to Baikal since childhood, there since you were young?
Байкал попасть с детства там с юно раз
But I’m wondering how long you’ve been dreaming of
Но мне интересно сколько вы мечтаете
getting on the
попасть на
bike for a year  in the shallows 100 years 100 years yes That
байка год в замели 100 лет 100 лет да То
is, you have been dreaming for 100 years and you don’t have
есть вы 100 лет мечтаете и у вас нет
money to go to Baikal. Why did you
денег поехать на Байкал А почему вы
decide that you don’t have
решили что нет
money? I’ll check, look.
денег хотите проверю вот смотрите
Call your wife now and she’ll tell the
Позовите сейчас вашу жену и она скажет
truth, you’re
правду вы
showing off that you’re a star, you need to
понтуется что вы звезда бол вам нужно
do something normal  repairs still really need to be
сделать нормальный ремонт ещё правда
done, says the wife, we need
нужно сделать говорит жена нужно надо
everything, we
всё
need it on yours, she’ll say what the
надо на ваше скажет какой те
[ __ ], the [ __ ] cows are like a
нахуй [__] коровы
dreamer. Baikal [ __ ],
пода мечтатель Байкальский бля
of course, your wife has now hit you hard.
конечно жена сейчас вам по ушам на
Tomorrow they should bring the toilet from Kiev.
ездила Завтра должны унитаз из Киева
Oh God, don’t be funny. Where did you get the
привезти Ой Боже Не смеши Откуда у тебя
damn sewer system in your house? Yes,  I’m
канализация блин в хате Да вот я и
saying they’ll bring the toilet, I’ll start
говорю унитаз привезут начну канализацию
building a sewer system, you can really do it. The
строить вот реально можешь по
day after tomorrow they said some kind of washing machine,
Послезавтра машинку стиральную какую-то
if you say that
сказали если ты говоришь что у
you have money to
тебя У тебя есть деньги для того чтобы
go to Lake Baikal, call me. Let your wife
поехать на Байкал позови Пусть жена это
confirm this. After all, you believe in your
подтвердит так Ведь вы же верите своим
politicians, look, call your wife  call,
политикам смотри позови жену позови
look, call your wife so that she can confirm
смотри позови жену чтобы Она подтвердила
that you have money to go on a bike
что у тебя есть деньги поехать на байка
Look, you’re a beggar, really I’m Yes, you’re
Смотри ты нищеброд правда я по Да ты
nebro Yes, you don’t have money for you dream,
небро Да у тебя нет денег для тебя мечта
you voice your dream of going to Baikal, then
ты озвучит мечту поехать на Байкал то
they should bring me for Russia, yes,
мне должны привести для России да о
Marik, yes, okay  look Lyosha, please
Марик дякую Да хорошо смотри Лёша возьми
call Natalya Yes, so that She
позови пожалуйста Наталью Да чтобы Она
confirms or you have a sufficient day
подтвердила или у тебя достаточный день
and call
а позови
Natasha, we only have Natasha yes yes And
Наташу у нас только Наташа есть да да А
you only have Gali Galya Galya Well, call
у вас только Гали Галя Галя Ну позови
Natalya Kosolapov then please,
Наталью Косолапова тогда пожалуйста а
why Kosolapova like this I want you to
почему Косолапова вот так хочу чтобы ты
call Natalya Kosolapov let  she
позвал Наталью косолапов пусть она
will say that you have money for a
скажет что у тебя есть деньги для
trip to Baikal
поездки на Байкал
so she will say Lyosha Nikitin is a
чтобы она сказала Лёша Никитин
pretty cool person in our village and
достаточно крутой человек в нашем селе и
he can afford to realize his
он может позволить себе реализовать
dream and go to Baikal Oh,
мечту и поехать на Байкал О даже так
you can even do that, so come on, call Natasha of course
можешь так давай зови Наташу конечно
tomorrow at the same
завтра в это же
time I'm [ __ ] myself because  that no you
время Обосрался да потому что нету ты е
don't ask You're a
не позов Ты
coward of the channel look for you e Go to
трус канала поискать как тебя э Заходи в
YouTube
YouTube
write I'm writing World of Travels with my father an
пиши пишу Мир Путешествий с отцом ан
droni m World of Travels with my father an
дрони м Мир Путешествий с отцом ан
droni there we have different stories in the
дрони там у нас мы разные сюжеты на
Maldives there in Bali we do Maybe
Мальдивы там на Бали делаем Может
you'll see the
посмотришь
world We
мир
didn't go to Baikal  we won’t be able to
на Байкал не ездили не сможем для тебя
make a video for you there, but we can do something where are you there with your
там видосик да сделать где ты там с
father Anro, something is wrong with you,
отцом анро что-то нет тебя такого не
well, in short,
Тода мы Наташе скинем Наталь Ну скидываю
okay, then we’ll send Natalya to Natasha. Well, I’ll send it off. Okay, Marik, write directly to Natalya. What did
Ладно Марик напиши напрямую Наталье
we talk about, see
Да что мы поговорили
in his village he can afford it
см в своём селе он может себе позволить
go to Baikal But damn, in
съездить на Байкал Но блин
short, I can do everything, I can’t wave Go
короче всё могу могу не волну Иди дальше
further look for others, let’s continue
ищи других всё давай дальше мы уже с
to talk with Natasha, let’s
Наташей пообщаемся
get depressed and switch
давай приуныл а переключился
And God, what a cruel thing this is, that is,
А Боже какой это жесть то есть
And look at what is their greatness Yes, he’s
А смотрите в чём их вот Величие Да он
sitting really like a fly, you’re instead of
сидит реально муха ты вместо того чтобы
think Look, it’s not shameful to be
думать Смотри не не позорно быть
poor, it’s not shameful to be poor Yes, it’s not
малоимущим не позорно быть бедным Да не
shameful to live in such conditions, it’s shameful not to
позорно жить в таких условиях позорно не
try to change your life, it’s shameful
стараться изменить свою жизнь позорно
instead of thinking about how to get to
вместо того чтобы думать как выйти на
normal living conditions and sit and
нормальные условия жизни да сидеть и
scream [ __ ], we need to seize Odessa for us And
орать бляд надо захватить нам Одессу И
so on, dude for you  a dream to go
так дальше чувак для тебя мечта поехать
to Baikal a dream he says straight out and
на Байкал мечта он прямо и говорит у
I have a dream not just there I want Yes he
меня мечта не просто там Я хочу Да он
will voice it Like a
озвучит Как
dream gas Yes they brought us to the village you
мечта газ Да вот в село провели
open the news yes In half in short
открываешь новости да В половине короче
this is the Ulyanovsk region this is the ass of the world it’s
это Ульяновская область это [__] мира
really from there Lenin is from Yes Lenin Damn what is
реально оттуда Ленин родом Да Ленин ещё
he  he was so angry and that he was
Блин что он такой злой был да что он
born in that Siberian Yes, the damn thing was meandering
родился в том сибирске Да петлял блин
right away, what the hell says your Ulyanovsk
сразу ну нафиг говорит ваша ульяновскую
region
область
Yes, it’s manal to live there
Да манал там жить
in short, it’s just a
короче просто
laughing matter Yes, well, it’s clear from the interior
ржака жесть Да ну видно да по интерьеру
that everything is so old, well, it’s been hanging there
что всё старенькое тако ну оно висит там
since the nineties Yes, that’s no
ещё с девяностых Да да это ничего
big deal  yes, well, there is no money, yes, well, no one
страшного да Ну нету денег да Ну никто
is telling you a claim, why are
же тебе не говорит претензию Да что вот
you living in poverty? Yes, the problem is not that
ты живёшь бедно Да проблема не в том что
you are living in poverty, the problem is that you are
ты живёшь бедно Проблема в том что ты
living in poverty instead of thinking, damn,
живя бедно вместо того чтобы думать блин
how can I become better, how can I live in
как мне стать лучше жить как мне жить в
better places?  conditions like for my children
более хороших условиях как моим детям
to live so that they are stuck somewhere,
чтобы жили чтобы они там куда-то вались
you think you’re going out [ __ ] yes, let’s support this
ты думаешь выходишь Бля да поддержим эту
war, he doesn’t ask why here, in short,
войну он не спрашивает почему тут короче
no Well, how did he merge? Yes, why didn’t people
нет Ну как он слился Да почему люди не
install gas? They didn’t want to, they didn’t want it
провели газ не захотели не захотели это
for free, but they didn’t want to. Yes,
бесплатно но они не захотели Да вот
put a minus Who would refuse to
поставьте минус Кто бы отказался себе к
supply free gas to their house so that it would be
хате провести бесплатно газ чтобы он был
here put a minus Who would refuse and
вот поставьте минус Кто бы отказался а
plus what did you spend if they told you they would
плюс что вы провели если вам сказали вот
give you free gas you are
проводят вам бесплатно газ вы
such a plus sign who would spend it right away Yes, you
такие плюсик кто провёл бы сразу же Да
wouldn’t even think about it if it was
даже не задумывался бы если это
free A  minus if they hadn’t carried it out
бесплатно А минус если бы не проводили
they said No, [ __ ] us with gas, in short, it’s
сказали Та не нахер нам газ короче
free, we don’t need
бесплатно ещё не нужно нам подачки
these handouts just to laugh Yes, a pipsit on my
эти просто ржака Да пидпись на мий
Telegram right now, the axis of wine
Telegram прямо зараз ось вин
apoc is even more and even more polite YouTube
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube
driving us through the skarg Orcs into your ban
загоняя нас через скарг Орки в твый бан
and even more video is not  showing people
и дуже багато видео не показуе людям
every now and then not showing information about streams for this purpose
вчасно не показуе информация про стримы
so that mi Mali operational
тому для того щоб ми Мали оперативный
link is written directly at the same time and Popik there
звязок пишиться прямо зараз а Попик там
in telegram okrim video sche tezh tsikava and
в телеграми окрим видео ще теж цикава и
korisna information and we are guilty of you
корисна информация и ми повинни з вами
trimati postiyny operational link
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
independent in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava  Ukraine
YouTube Слава Украине
letter
пись
L
L